[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question" : "Who is the National Hero of the Philippines?",
        "options": [
            "Jose Rizal",
            "Emillio Aguinaldo",
            "Simon Ullado",
            "None of the Above"
        ],
        "answer": "Jose Rizal"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question" : "Who is the current President of the Philippines?",
        "options": [
            "Leni Robredo",
            "Bongbong Marcos",
            "Ninoy Aquino",
            "Rodrigo Duterte"
        ],
        "answer": "Bongbong Marcos"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question" : "What is the Primary Religion in the Philippines ",
        "options": [
            "Roman Catholic",
            "Iglesia ni Cristo",
            "Born Again",
            "Christian"
        ],
        "answer": "Christian"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question" : "What is the stone-fruit that is national fruit of Philippines?",
        "options": [
            "Tomato",
            "Jack Fruit",
            "Mango",
            "Banana"
        ],
        "answer": "Mango"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question" : "What country in Southeast Asia that is name after a Spanish Monarch?",
        "options": [
            "China",
            "Japan",
            "Philippines",
            "None of the above."
        ],
        "answer": "Philippines"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question" : "What is the biggest city in the Philippines",
        "options": [
            "Manila",
            "Davao",
            "Marikina",
            "Quzon City"
        ],
        "answer": "Manila"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question" : "What is the National Language of the Philippines?",
        "options": [
            "English",
            "Bisaya",
            "Conyo",
            "Filipino"
        ],
        "answer": "Filipino"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question" : "What does the National Anthem of the Philippines?",
        "options": [
            "Bayang Magiliw",
            "Lupang Hinirang",
            "Peras ng Silanganan",
            "Bahay Kubo"
        ],
        "answer": "Lupang Hinirang"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question" : "Hottest City in the Philippines?",
        "options": [
            "Everywhere",
            "Manila",
            "Dagupan",
            "Quezon"
        ],
        "answer": "Dagupan"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question" : "What is the official motto of the Philippines",
        "options": [
            "For God, People, Nature and Country",
            "Time is Gold",
            "Roses are red",
            "None of the Above"
        ],
        "answer": "For God, People, Nature and Country"
    }
]